$C7Everything you type will be filtered.

Dollar signs will become tab chars, which can be
used to color team names and info boards.
To color your text, type %sCx, where x is a
value from the Text Colors list.

Pound signs (number signs) will become returns
(newlines).

A percent sign will create a special character.
Typing a percent sign followed by one of these
letters will make one of these special characters:
%%d = %d      %%x = %x      %%p = %p      %%+ = %+
%%1 = %1      %%2 = %2      %%3 = %3      %%c = %c
%%l = %l      %%y = %y      %%X = %X      %%Y = %Y
%%Z = %Z      %%? = %?      %%C = %C      %%R = %R
%%s = %s      %%%% = %%      %%n = %n