Using the %sitem command

For PSOBB, the %sitem command is used to create
items. Use it like this:

%sitem <item code in hexadecimal>

The item code must be from 2 to 16 bytes (4 to 32
characters) of hexadecimal data. Any bytes you
omit will become zeroes.

The item that you specify will appear from the next
enemy you kill or box you break.

To create meseta, use the command like this:

%sitem 04000000 %n0 %n0 <amount>