Using the %sbbchar command

%sbbchar is used to convert a character from an
older version of PSO to Blue Burst format and save
it on this server. Use the command like this:

%sbbchar <username> <password> <slot>

If the username and password are correct, the
character that you're currently playing as will be
converted to PSOBB format and saved under that
account, in the specified character slot.